familyfreshmeals.com 2018-03-02

# Privacy Policy - Family Fresh Meals

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Family Fresh Meals collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://familyfreshmeals website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered.

## Personal identification information

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities (such as giveaways or contests).

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## How we use collected information

Family Fresh Meals collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them — i.e. to notify giveaway winners.  
– To send periodic emails  
The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their direct inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

## Sharing your personal information

We **do not** sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## Third party websites

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

## Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Changes to this privacy policy

Family Fresh Meals has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting Me

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact me at:  
corey@familyfreshmeals.com

This document was last updated on October 27, 2016

Privacy policy created by Generate Privacy Policy
